<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>North Central CT and Western MA's Best Real Estate Training - Lori Gabriel</title>
    <description>Lori Gabriel, a top Real Estate Agent in North Central CT and Western MA, shares her own internal real estate agent training for free. Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 13:14:17 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 13:14:17 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Kayla Zimmerman Became an Agent</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/foPikkRViUQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Kayla Zimmerman’s story of how she joined Team Gabriel as a new agent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today Kayla Zimmerman is sharing her experience of joining Team Gabriel and working with us:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“I always knew I wanted to be a Realtor; I just didn’t know where to start.&lt;/strong&gt; When I found Team Gabriel, I applied to be an assistant, but when Lori and Joe interviewed me, they decided I would make a good Realtor. I joined the team in August 2020 during the pandemic. They were very supportive, and I was excited to jump right into being a real estate agent because that was my ultimate goal.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I love the daily support we get.%20http://localhost:4000/how-kayla-zimmerman-became-an-agent.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I love the daily support we get.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“They walked me through all the steps of how to get my license and got me settled into the job of a Realtor. I got my license for Connecticut and Massachusetts, and I love my job. Team Gabriel was very helpful with everything I needed, and I love the daily support we get; they’re always there to answer questions or help with any challenges we face. &lt;strong&gt;They help us reach our goals, cheer us on, and congratulate us when we succeed. “&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“So far this year, I’ve sold 15 houses, which wouldn’t have been possible on any other team. I wouldn’t be where I am today without Team Gabriel. If you’re considering becoming a Realtor, I 100% recommend working with them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like to hear more about joining our team, call or email us. We would love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 09:17:47 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-kayla-zimmerman-became-an-agent.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-kayla-zimmerman-became-an-agent.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Michelle O’Leary Joined Team Gabriel</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rGqJ_qxmtY4?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center; font-style:italic;&quot;&gt;Michelle talks about why she got into real estate and joined our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why work with our team? Today our agent Michelle O’Leary is discussing how she got into real estate and what drew her to Team Gabriel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Michelle worked in retail management for about 10 years before getting into real estate&lt;/strong&gt;, but she always has an interest in homes and being an agent. It wasn’t until she and her finance purchased their first home five years ago that she got intrigued with the process. She figured it must be super rewarding to help first-time homebuyers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually, she decided to leave her salary job and worked part-time to take real estate classes because she wanted to change, be uncomfortable, and learn from the experience. After she got her license, &lt;strong&gt;she interviewed with a lot of different brokers.&lt;/strong&gt; None of them had what she was looking for until she stumbled across us at Team Gabriel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=They provided me with training and leads so I could get out there and help people fulfill their goals of homeownership.%20http://localhost:4000/why-michelle-oleary-joined-team-gabriel.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“They provided me with training and leads so I could get out there and help people fulfill their goals of homeownership.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was so impressed with what we had to offer that she scheduled a meeting with us. She said that she felt like she was part of the team within 20 minutes of our conversation. We were a good fit for her as a first-time agent who needed someone to help lead them. The other brokerages had no training or accountability to offer her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Michelle, &lt;strong&gt;the best part about being on a team is that there is constant contact.&lt;/strong&gt; Someone can always answer your questions or help you. She loves the connection and collective brainstorming that happens on our team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were days when she could devote herself fully to real estate and days she couldn’t. However, she appreciated that no matter the day, we could teach, train, and provide her with leads. She had someone to help lead her to that ultimate, satisfying goal of handing someone the keys to their new home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to join a team or get into real estate, join Team Gabriel. Whether you’re a new or experienced agent, we can help train you as we did with Michelle. Just give us a call.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-michelle-oleary-joined-team-gabriel.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/why-michelle-oleary-joined-team-gabriel.html</guid>
        
        <category>Testimonial</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sharon’s First Experiences in Real Estate</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3ZThmgze1gA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here are agent Sharon’s experiences and why she joined our team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharon, an agent on our team, told us about her real estate experience and why she came to work for us:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The reason I got into real estate was that I had two children and wanted a more flexible schedule. I wanted to be home for my newborn and when my son got off the school bus every day. However, the principal challenge when I began real estate was that I thought I would make my own schedule, but it turned out I was working morning, noon, night, and weekends, and trying to juggle family life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=I love working with people and helping them find the ideal home.%20http://localhost:4000/sharons-first-experiences-in-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“I love working with people and helping them find the ideal home.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real estate started getting exciting when I met people and helped them through every step of the process&lt;/strong&gt; of one of the largest investments of their lives. My motivation is wanting to help people, and I’m sticking with it now. Unfortunately, back in 2007 when the market crashed, I had to make the decision to go back to my previous job, healthcare management. However, once the market began to recover, I was ready to get back into real estate. I loved working with people and helping them find the ideal home for their families. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later, my family relocated to Connecticut, and I knew I wanted to continue working in real estate. Being new to the area, I knew that was going to be a challenge, so I wanted to join a team. When I came to meet Team Gabriel I saw they were easy to work with, down to earth, and it seemed like the perfect team for me. The training was great, it wasn’t hard to adjust to this new environment, they made it easy, and &lt;strong&gt;I’m very happy to be a part of their team.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting a career in real estate is a challenge, but as long as you have structure and routine, and you follow those, you’ll be successful.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about our team or want to see if we’re the right fit for you, call or email us. We would love to speak with you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 11:34:39 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/sharons-first-experiences-in-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/sharons-first-experiences-in-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        <category>Testimonial</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
